import { Deck } from "../types";

/** Data Source: https://www.oxfordlearnersdictionaries.com/us/about/pronunciation_american_english */
export const decks: Deck[] = [
  {
    _id: 0,
    name: "English Practice: Vowels",
    description:
      "Oxford Advanced American Dictionary Pronunciation Guide: Vowels",
    cards: [
      {
        _id: 0,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/si/",
        back: "see",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 1,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/sɪt/",
        back: "sit",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 2,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/tɛn/",
        back: "ten",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 3,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/kæt/",
        back: "cat",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 4,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/hɑt/",
        back: "hot",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 5,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/sɔ/",
        back: "saw",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 6,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/pʊt/",
        back: "put",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 7,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/tu/",
        back: "too",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 8,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/kʌp/",
        back: "cup",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 9,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/əˈbaʊt/",
        back: "about",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 10,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/seɪ/",
        back: "say",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 11,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/faɪv/",
        back: "five",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 12,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/bɔɪ/",
        back: "boy",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 13,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/naʊ/",
        back: "now",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 14,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/ɡoʊ/",
        back: "go",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 15,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/bərd/",
        back: "bird",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 16,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/nɪr/",
        back: "near",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 17,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/hɛr/",
        back: "hair",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 18,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/kɑr/",
        back: "car",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 19,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/nɔrθ/",
        back: "north",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 20,
        _deckId: 0,
        front: "/tʊr/",
        back: "tour",
        days: 0,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    _id: 1,
    name: "English Practice: Consonants",
    description:
      "Oxford Advanced American Dictionary Pronunciation Guide: Consonants",
    cards: [
      {
        _id: 0,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/pɛn/",
        back: "pen",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 1,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/bæd/",
        back: "bad",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 2,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/ti/",
        back: "tea",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 3,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/ˈbʌt̮ər/",
        back: "butter",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 4,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/dɪd/",
        back: "did",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 5,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/kæt/",
        back: "cat",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 6,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/ɡɑt/",
        back: "got",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 7,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/tʃɪn/",
        back: "chin",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 8,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/dʒun/",
        back: "June",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 9,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/fɔl/",
        back: "fall",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 10,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/vɔɪs/",
        back: "voice",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 11,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/θɪn/",
        back: "thin",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 12,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/ðɛn/",
        back: "then",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 13,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/soʊ/",
        back: "so",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 14,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/zu/",
        back: "zoo",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 15,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/ʃi/",
        back: "she",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 16,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/ˈvɪʒn/",
        back: "vision",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 17,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/haʊ/",
        back: "how",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 18,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/mæn/",
        back: "man",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 19,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/noʊ/",
        back: "no",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 20,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/sɪŋ/",
        back: "sing",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 21,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/lɛɡ/",
        back: "leg",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 22,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/rɛd/",
        back: "red",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 23,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/yɛs/",
        back: "yes",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 24,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/wɛt/",
        back: "wet",
        days: 0,
      },
      {
        _id: 25,
        _deckId: 1,
        front: "/ˈxɑnəkə/",
        back: "Chanukah",
        days: 0,
      },
    ],
  },
];
